A Guide to the Papers of the League of Women Voters of Hampton Roads, 1956-1999
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Business and Organization
  - Structure and Organzation
    - LWV Reference Book, 1983-84 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 11)
    - LWV US-"Local League Handbook," 1969 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Welcome to the LWV, 1970 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 13)
    - In League: LWV US (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Concurrence Definition (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Consensus Definition (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Consensus Forms (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 17)
    - President's Packet, 1986 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 18)
    - LWV Prospectus: A Planning Guide for Local and State Leagues #4, 1980-1982 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 19)
    - LWV Prospectus: A Planning Guide for Local and State Leagues #1 & #2, 1982-1984 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 1)
    - LWV Prospectus: A Planning Guide for Local and State Leagues #1 & #3, 1984-1986 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 2)
    - LWV Prospectus, 1984-1986 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Guidelines: League Appointments to goverment agencies, commissions (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Program Coordination and Management (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Observer Training Manual, 1970 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Leader Manuals & Guidelines (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Training Material (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Membership
    - LWV Office State & National, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Membership Information (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Membership Handbook, 1965-1967 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 11)
    - LWV Membership Booklet, 1990-1992 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Membership I (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Membership II (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Membership Recruitment, 1987-1990 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Membership and Prospect List, February 23, 1988 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Membership Lists, 1969-1986 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Membership Roster, 1975-1988 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Membership Roster, 1989-1994 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Reference Book and Directory, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Reference Book and Directory, 1990-1991 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Reference Book and Directory, 1995-1996 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Membership Reports (to National) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Tree, 1982 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Local League Mailing Information, 1989 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Financing
    - Finance Development (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Development (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 11)
    - LWV Financing, 1972-1976 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 12)
    - PMP (per member payment) and Pledges, Dues, 1971-1979 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Finance Chairman Calendar, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1957-1960 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1961-1965 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1966-1970 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1971-1975 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1976-1980 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1981-1985 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1986-1990 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, 1991-1996 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Budget/Treasurer's Report, undated (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Publicity and Public Relations
    - Publicity, 1988-1995 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
    - LWV Publicity (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Media Contacts (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations: Press Releases, Correspondence I, 1967-1973 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Public Relations: Press Releases, Correspondence II, 1974-1986 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases concerning Public Releations (National), 1972-1980 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Public Relations: League of Women Voters Publications (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Sample Slogans (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Logos (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Business
    - LWV Calendars (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Committee Reports-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Community Outreach (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Neighborhood Assistance Program" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Crossroads: National Project (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Self-study (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Disbanding of Portsmouth & Chesapeake Leagues (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Inter League Organization (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Litigation (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Plan (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Region III Leagues (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Soviets Visit Hampton Roads, includes pictures with Meyera Obendorf, Mayor of Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Teleconference, October 13, 1990 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Virginia Women's Legacies" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Business (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Events (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 18)
  - League History
    - History (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 19)
    - LWV: "A Great Idea Through the Years" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 20)
    - News Articles Concerning LWV History (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 21)
    - (History) The Humble Way 3rd Quarter, 1968 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Women's History (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations
    - City Employee Represenative Election (ERC), 1989 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Common Cause of Virginia (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Princess Anne Women's Club (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Pro-Choice Alliance (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Society of Environmental Toxicology and Chemistry (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Vietnam Veteran's National Election I (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Vietnam Veteran's National Election II (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 30)
- Meetings and Conventions
  - Annual Meetings
    - Annual Meeting: March 30, 1966 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting: March 20, 1968 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting: March 31, 1969 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting: March 31, 1970 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting: March 24, 1971 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting: March 23, 1972 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting: March 21, 1973 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting: March 27, 1974 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting: March 13, 1975 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting: March 17, 1976 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting: March 16, 1977 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting: March 16, 1978 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting: March 21, 1979 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting: March 29, 1980 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting: March 28, 1981 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting: March 27, 1982 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting: March 19, 1983 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting: April 13, 1985 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting: April 15, 1986 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting [Loudoun County]: April 21, 1986 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting: April 22, 1987 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting: April 27, 1988 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting: April 18, 1989 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting: May, 1990 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meeting: May 11, 1991 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting: May 9, 1992 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting: May 22, 1993 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Annual Meeting: May 21, 1994 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting: April 22, 1995 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting: May 2, 1996 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Annual Reports: 1965-1966 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports: 1966-1967 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports: 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports: 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports: 1969-1970 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports: 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports: 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports: 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports: 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports: 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports: 1975-1976 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports: 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports: 1977-1978 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports: 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports: 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports: 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports: 1981-1982 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports: 1984-1985 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports: 1987-1988 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report: May 2, 1996 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report: May 1, 1997 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Local Board
    - Board of Directors (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
    - LWV-Norfolk & Virginia Beach: Board of Directors, Policies & Procedures, 1985 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
    - LWV-Norfolk & Virginia Beach: Board of Directors, Policies & Procedures, 1994-1995 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Board Packets (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Board Tools/Handbook (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Board Tools/Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Board Nominating Committee 1960s (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Board Nominating Committee 1970s (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Board Nominating Committee 1980s (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Board Orienation I (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Board Orienation II (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "How to Get Your Board a Plan"-A Checklist- 1980 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Board Related, 1983-1986 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Board Lists, 1957-1970 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Board Lists, 1971-1975 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Board Lists, 1976-1980 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Board Lists, 1981-1985 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Board Lists, 1986-1988 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Board Lists, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1956 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1957 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1962 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1963 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1964 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1965 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1966 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1967 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1968 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1969 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1970 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1971 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1975 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1981 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1982 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1983 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1985 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1986 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1988 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1989 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1990 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1991 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1992 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1993 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1994 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1995 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Local Board Agendas & Minutes, 1996 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Local Board Minutes, March 7, 1998 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
  - State Board/Council
    - Minutes (State Board), 1978-1982 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
    - State Council Meetings: 1980, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Board
    - National Board Report, 1969 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
    - National Board Report, 1970 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
    - National Board Report, 1971 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
    - National Board Reports, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
    - National Board Reports, 1974 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
    - National Board Reports, 1975 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
    - National Board Reports, 1976 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
    - National Board Reports, 1977 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
    - National Board Reports, 1978 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1977-1980 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1981-1982 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1985-1986 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1989 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Post Board Summaries, 1995 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Conventions
    - State Convention, 1981 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 16)
    - State Convention, 1985 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 17)
    - State Convention, 1987 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 18)
    - LWV of Virginia Convention, Willamsburg, 1989 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 19)
    - National Convention, 1986 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 20)
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: National to State and Local, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: State (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Consultant, 1977, 1979-1982, 1989 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Environmental Issues 1970-1973 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Legislative [Congress] (majority with G. William Whitehurst) 1969-1972 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Legislative [Congress] (majority with G. William Whitehurst) 1973-1987 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Publicity and Meetings I (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Publicity and Meetings II (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 22)
- Newsletters
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach LWV Bulletin, 1956, 1967 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach LWV Bulletin, 1970 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1971 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1972 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1973 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1974 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1975 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1978 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1980 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Norfolk-Virginia Beach Voter LWV Bulletin, 1981-1983, 1986 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Voter, May, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Voter, 1988 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Voter, 1989 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Voter, 1990 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Voter, 1994-1995 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Voter, 1996 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Voter, 1998-February 1999 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Guidelines for Voter Articles (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Voter, 1972, 1973, 1976 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Voter, 1977-87 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Voter, Summer 1987 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Voter, 1989 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Voter, 1990 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Voter (Fall, Vol. 40, #5), 1993 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Voter, 1994 & 1995 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 11)
  - National Voter, 1997 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Swap Shop, 1957-1965 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 13)
  - League of Women Voters South Hampton Roads Reports to Community, Winter, 1994-1995 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 14)
  - LWV Community Guides, 1977 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 15)
  - LWV of Virginia: Legislative Newsletter, 1980-1987 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 16)
  - League of Women Voters of Loudoun County, October, 1995 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 17)
  - AERS News, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Scientists, 1992-1997 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Virginians for Returnables, 1982 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 20)
- Programs and Projects
  - General Program Information
    - Program Management I (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Program Management II (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 3)
    - LWV National Programs (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Programs w/co-sponsors (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Action
    - Action I (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Action II (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 7)
    - LWVUS: Action, 1978 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Action Alerts: Calls for Action [1980s] (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Action Testimony I, 1957-1975 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Action Testimony II, 1977-1986 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Action Testimony III, 1987-1990 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Action Testimony IV, 1991-1997 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Action Testimony, undated (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Presentations on Issues (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Bond Issue 1968 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Civil Rights Restoration Act (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Committee to Preserve Assateague (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 18)
    - VA ERA-"Women of Virginia: Rights You Are Denied" (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Action: Motor Voter (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Superfund Call to Action (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Action-various issues (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Legislative-Lobbying (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 23)
    - State Legislative Action [Forms and Information] (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Legislative Action/Bill of Rights (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Legislative Previews/Wrap-Ups, 1978,1988-1989,1991-1996 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Action: Correspondence-General Assembly, Senate (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Concerning Legislative Action, 1987 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Various Newspaper Clippings (Action) (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Action: Letters to Editors (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Education Fund
    - LWVUS Education Fund (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 6)
    - LWV Education Fund, 1960-1989 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 7)
    - LWV Education Fund: Brochures & Annual Reports, 1967-1976 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 8)
    - LWV Education Fund: Newsletter, 1965-1966 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Education Fund: Bicentennial Bill of Rights I (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Education Fund: Bicentennial Bill of Rights II (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Education Fund: Bicentennial Bill of Rights III (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 12)
    - UN Wrap Up, 1989 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Census, 1990 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Expense Voucher I: LWV Education Fund (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Expense Voucher II: LWV Education Fund (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Overseas Education Fund (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Speakers Bureau
    - Speakers Bureau [speeches] (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 18)
- Voters Service
  - Voter Registration
    - Voter Registration Month, 1974 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Voter Registration Drive, 1976 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Voter Registration, 1984 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Voter Registration Efforts, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Voter Registration [1990s] (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Mail-in Voter Registration, 1996 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Voter Registration-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk Ward System, 1992 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 8)
    - LWV Goverment Week, 1976 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 9)
    - America Vote, 1976 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Votingist City-Local, 1976 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "Take Back the System" Campaign, 1992 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Brochure "Take Back the System," 1992 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Get Out & Vote!"-Encouraging Voter Participation in Your Community (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Election Laws
    - Election Laws: Voting Rights Act-National (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Election Laws: 1965, 1970, 1973, 1974 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Election Laws: 1975-1976, 1978 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Election Laws: 1984 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Election Laws: 1985-1986 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Voting Rights Act, 1981-1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Access to Registration and Voting: Continuing Obstacles" (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Voting Information
    - Voting Information and Calendars, 1954-1972 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Voting Information, 1973-1976 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Voting Information, 1977 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Voting Information, 1978 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Facts for Voters, 1989 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 8)